===============OP=================
===============ED=================
皇暦2018年
Imperial Calendar year 2018.
世界制覇を進める神聖ブリタニア帝国の前に
In the face of the creeping world
domination of the Holy Britannian Empire,
一人のテロリストが復活した
a lone terrorist has been resurrected.
その名はゼロ
His name is Zero.
謎の少女C.C.から手に入れた絶対順守の力ギアスを使い
Using Geass, the absolute power to command
given to him by the mysterious girl C.C.,
ゼロは再び抗いを決意する
Zero is determined to once again resist them.
植民地エリア11となった日本から始まるこのさざ波が
These ripples which begin in Japan,
now known as the colony Area 11...
時代に　そして人々に何を残すのか
How will they affect the age,
and the hearts of various people?
今はまだ誰も知らない
For the moment, no one knows.
朝も夜も恋い焦がれて
Asa mo yoru mo koikogarete
Morning and night, I long for you
星になるよ 君守る
hoshi ni naru yo kimi mamoru
I'll become a star and protect you
戦いは行方知らず
tatakai wa yukue shirazu
No matter where the battle may take me
明日と昨日の交差点で
ashita to kinou no kousaten de
At the intersection of tomorrow and yesterday
交わらない君と僕
majiwaranai kimi to boku
You and I can't be together
今行くよ 僕は流れ星
ima iku yo boku wa nagareboshi
I'm a shooting star, on my way right now
世界が朽ち果てても 変わることの無いものがある
sekai ga kuchihatetemo
Even if the world crumbles apart
kawaru koto no nai mono ga aru
There are things which will never change
涙を堪えてでも 守るべきものが僕らにはある
namida wo koraete demo
Even as we bear tears in our eyes
mamorubeki mono ga bokura ni wa aru
There are things we must protect
（nononono）
nanman'nen nan'okunen mae kara no
A message that's been in my body
遅れまいと メッセージが絶えない
（no）
message ga tainai de
For thousands and millions of years,
剥き出す 撃ち抜く
（迷いは無い）
uzukidasu... mayoi wa nai
Springs out... I have no reservations
（簡単だ）
narihibiku... kantan da
Roars out... It's easy
しゃがれた声で 傷だらけの手で 君守る
shagareta koe de... asu wo yobu
In a hoarse voice... Calling tomorrow
kizudarake no te de... kimi mamoru
With my wounded hands... I protect you
way got you could like
I continue to fight...
I continue to fight!
朝も夜も恋い焦がれて
asa mo yoru mo koikogarete
Morning and night, I long for you
星になるよ 君守る
hoshi ni naru yo kimi mamoru
I'll become a star and protect you
戦いは行方知らず
tatakai wa yukue shirazu
No matter where the battle may take me
明日と昨日の交差点で
ashita to kinou no kousaten de
At the intersection of tomorrow and yesterday
交わらない君と僕
majiwaranai kimi to boku
You and I can't be together
宿命を切り裂く流れ星
sadame wo kirisaku nagareboshi
I'm a shooting star, tearing fate apart
溢れる君の涙 僕が今奪い去る
afureru kimi no namida boku ga ima ubaisaru
I'll take away your overflowing tears right now
PLAN FOR INDEPENDENT JAPAN
先行して突入した　機情局は？
What's the status of the O.S.I.
forces who broke in first?
連絡はいまだ
No contact with them as yet.
チャフの濃度は下がっているはずだ
（チャフ　chaff）
The chaff density should be
dropping now. Recon section 4!
第4偵察局
黒の騎士団と思われるテロリストは
The terrorists believed to be the Black
Knights remain fighting inside of Babel Tower.
バベルタワーに立てこもったままです
敵性ナイトメアフレームの存在を確認
We have confirmed the presence
of enemy Knightmare Frames.
よし　第7特装師団は下方より突入せよ
All right, special equipment
section 7 will break in from below.
イエス　マイ　ロード
Yes, My Lord!
もう無理だ　逃げよう
This is hopeless! Let's run for it!
もう少し　持ちこたえて
Just hold out a little longer!
ゼロが　ここの構造をつかむまで
Just until Zero can get the building layout!
私たちも援護に回るから
We're going to back you up, too!
ルルーシュ
Lelouch...
そうだ　オレが　ゼロだ
Yes, I'm Zero.
ゼロ
Zero!
こいつは　ルルーシュだ
It's Lelouch!
日本人を　君を利用した男だ
The man who's used the Japanese people!
Who's used you!
そんな男を守りたいのか　君は
You want to defend a man like that?! You?!
ゼロ　君を終わらせる
Zero... This is the end of you.
オレは過去の自分に　朱雀に敗れた
I was... I was defeated by the old me. By Suzaku.
そしてあいつに…
And then he...
ブリタニア皇帝の前に　引き出された
He dragged me before the Britannian Emperor!
元第17皇位継承者
The former 17th heir to the imperial throne...
Lelouch vi Britannia.
ルルーシュ·ヴィ·ブリタニア
久しいな　我が息子よ
It's been a long time, hasn't it, my son?
You... You god damned!
き　貴様
ギアスは使わせない
You won't use your Geass!
恐れながら申し上げます
I have a request.
陛下　自分を帝国最強の十二騎士
Allow me to join the Knights of the Round,
the 12 strongest knights in the empire!
ナイトオブラウンズにお加えください
ゼロを捕らえた褒美をよこせと？
As reward for your capturing Zero?
お前…
You!
言ったはずだよ　ルルーシュ
I told you before, Lelouch.
オレは　中からこの世界を変えると
That I was going to change this
world from inside the system.
友達を売って　出世するのか
Even if it means selling out your friends to advance?!
そうだ
Yes.
よかろう　今の答え　気に入った
Very well. I like the answer you just gave.
では　ナイトオブラウンズに命じる
Well then, as a Knight of the Round, I order you.
ゼロの左目をふさげ
Cover Zero's left eye.
イエス　ユア　マジェスティ
Yes, Your Majesty.
皇子でありながら反旗を翻した不肖の息子
My unworthy son, who raised the banner
of rebellion although he was a prince.
だが　まだ使い道はある
Still, there is another use for him.
な…何
Wh-What?!
記憶を書き換える
I will rewrite your memory.
ゼロであること　マリアンヌのこと
About being Zero, about Marianne,
and about Nunnally.
ナナリーのこと
まさか…ギアス？！
Impossible... Geass?!
すべてを忘れ　ただ人となるがよい
Forget it all and become an ordinary person.
やめろ　また　オレから奪うつもりか
Stop! You're going to steal from me again?!
母さんを　ナナリーまで
First my mother, now Nunnally?!
シャルル·ジ·ブリタニアが刻む
Charles zi Britannia engraves into you...
やめろ
STOP!!!
新たなる偽りの記憶を
a new, false set of memories!
C.C.
C.C....
私ではない　あの男にギアスを与えたのは
I wasn't the one who gave that man his Geass.
ナナリーはどこにいる
Where is Nunnally now?
お前の妹を捜そうにも
We tried to find your little sister, but with
the Black Knights all but destroyed, well...
黒の騎士団が壊滅状態ではな
咲世子はどうなった
What about Sayoko?
ディートハルトと共に中華連邦に逃れた
She ran off to the Chinese
Federation along with Diethard.
あの女は　ゼロの正体を知らない
She still doesn't know Zero's true identity.
ナナリーの重要性が分からずともしかたがないだろう
She can't be blamed when she didn't know
Nunnally's true importance, can she?
皇帝にギアスを与えたものを捜し出し
I'll find the one who gave the emperor
his Geass, and then take Nunnally back.
ナナリーを…
オレに妹はいるが　弟はいなかった
I had a younger sister,
but not a younger brother!
誰なんだ　あいつは
So, who is he?!
よかった　ブリタニア軍ですね
Thank goodness! You're Britannian soldiers,
right? I'm looking for my big brother.
兄さんを捜しているんですが…
建物の構造図はあっても
This has the layout of this building,
but no I.D. codes are written down.
認識番号のメモはないな
やはりこのナイトメアは使えないか
We can't use this Knightmare, either, can we?
そこで何をしている
What are you doing there?
その服　学生だな
That's a student uniform, isn't it?
軍人さんですか　助かった
A soldier? Thank goodness!
この人に早く手当てを
We need to help this man at once!
機密情報局の…
He's from the O.S.I. What are the
emperor's personal agents doing here?
皇帝陛下の直属に何があったんだ
よし　情報どおり
Good, just as my information said.
カラレスの軍は　オレのことを知らない
Calares's forces don't know about me.
使えるな　こいつのデータは
I can use the data in this thing.
生存者は一人だけか
There's only one survivor?
ええ
Yes. Only you.
あなただけです
何
What?
だから…
So...
よこせ　お前のナイトメアを
Give me your Knightmare.
分かった
Understood.
認識番号はQR5　YK1D6
The I.D. code is QR5-YK1D6.
ありがとう
Thank you.
ギアスは相手の目を直接見なければかからないとはいえ
I know you need direct sight of a person's
eyes to use your Geass, but still...
不老不死の魔女に言われたくはない
I don't want to hear that from
an immortal witch like you.
反撃している？　テロリストが？
They're counterattacking? The terrorists?
はい
Yes. It seems that they've seized
some of our Knightmares.
我が軍のナイトメアを鹵獲しているもようです
恥さらしな
How disgraceful.
しかし　敵は小勢
Still, their numbers are small.
よろしければ　私が
If I could possibly join the battle?
いや　君はあくまでも客将　預かりの身だ
No. You're still a guest here,
and under our protection.
ここは　総督である私が行くべきだろう
As viceroy, it's my place to go out there.
しかし…
But...
中華料理のスパイスは口に合わん
I don't care for the spices in Chinese food.
それに　いいものだろう
Besides, this is good for me.
人間狩りは
A man hunt.
はじけろ　ブリタニア
Let's see you pop, Britannian!
よくやった　Q1
Well done, Q1! Now head to the 21st floor.
次は　21階へ向かえ
P4は階段を封鎖しろ
P4, you cut off the stairs.
R5は左30度
R5, left, 30 degrees.
N1　そこから50メートル　天井に向けて斉射
N1, fire a barrage 50 meters
from you, toward the ceiling.
エミリオ卿　通信途絶
Contact lost with Lord Emilio!
IFFのコード変更を
（IFF　敵味方識別信号）
Change I.F.F. codes!
これで5回目です
We have! Five times already!
オルティス隊　全滅
Ortiz unit, wiped out!
バカな　一体誰がテロリストの指揮を
Impossible!
Who's directing these terrorists?!
何をやっている
What are you doing?
そ…総督…
V-Viceroy!
ゼロの正体が学生とはな
So, Zero's really just a student, huh?
しかし　やはり　物が違う
Even so, he's something special!
歩兵部隊　ゼロが奪ったサザーランドはまだ残っている
Ground troops! There's still one Sutherland
left that Zero stole! Get in it, fast!
早く乗り込め
ゼロさえいれば勝てる
With Zero with us, we can win!
奇跡は起きる　起きるんだ
He'll make a miracle for us! He will!
テロリストが！
Damned terrorists!
そろそろカラレス総督の出番かな
Shouldn't Viceroy Calares be
making his appearance, soon?
順調みたいね
Seems to be going well.
カレン　21階に向かえと
Kallen... I told you to head to the 21st floor.
あなたのそばに　いたかったの
I wanted to be at your side.
やっと　二人きりに　なれたわね
We're finally alone.
エリア11の餌に誰かが食いついたようだな
It would seem someone is nibbling
at the bait we left in Area 11.
C.C.ですか
Is it C.C., Majesty?
まだ　分からぬよ
We still don't know.
枢木
Kururugi, this is the first time even one
of the Rounds has been allowed in here.
ここに入れるのは　ラウンズでもお前が初めて
シュナイゼルたちも　知らぬ場所よ
Even Schneizel and the others
don't know of this place.
光栄です　陛下
I'm honored, Your Majesty. But, why me?
しかし　どうして　自分を
ラウンズの中でお前だけが知っている
Because you are the only
one of the Rounds who know.
ゼロの正体とギアスを
About Zero's true identity...
And about Geass.
ここは…神殿？
This place... Is it a temple?
違うな　これは…
Not at all.
This is... Yes.
This is a weapon for destroying God.
そう　神を滅ぼすための武器
武器？
A weapon?!
アーカーシャの剣という
It is called the Sword of Akasha.
神根島でゼロを見捨てた君が　なんの話だ
So, what do you, the one who abandoned
Zero at Kamine Island, want to say to me?
ルルーシュ　あなたはずっと私をだましていた
Lelouch... You lied to me the entire time.
ゼロが本当は君のクラスメートだったことか
About Zero actually being your classmate?
それともギアスの力のことか
Or about my Geass power?
両方よ
Both.
答えて　あなたは　私にもギアスを使ったの
Answer me! Did you use your Geass on me, too?!
私の心をねじ曲げて　従わせて
Did you twist my heart and make me your follower?!
ルルーシュ
Lelouch!
君の心は君自身のものだ
Your heart is yours alone.
ゼロへの忠誠もあこがれも　すべて
As was your loyalty and devotion to Zero.
動かないで
Don't move!
カレン　誇りに思っていい
Kallen, take pride in it.
君が　決めたんだ
You decided. You made the choice.
君が選んだんだ　この私を
To choose... me.
信じられないか
You can't believe it?
信じたい
I wanted to believe.
Enough to become a slave...
だから　奴隷になってでも…
そうか
I see.
でも　私が信じるのは　ゼロよ
But the one I believe in is Zero!
ルルーシュ　あんたなんかじゃない
It isn't you, Lelouch!
ああ　それでいい
Okay, fine with me. By the way...
ところで　いつまでその格好でいるつもりだ
Are you ever planning to change out of that?
み　見ないでよ　変態
D- Don't look at me, you pervert!
ゼロに向かって　その言い方は
You'd talk to Zero like that?
今のは　ルルーシュに言ったのよ
I'm saying it to Lelouch right now!
はいはい
Right, right.
どうした
What is it?
ブリタニアに援軍が現れた
Britannian reinforcements have shown up.
すごい数だ　どうすればいい
There's a ton of them! What do we do?
勝てっこねぇよ　こんなの
We can't beat this many!
何が起こってるの
What's happening?
第4特装より　降下開始します
Special equipment section 4 has begun to drop.
中華連邦に見せつけよ
Show the Chinese Federation!
Show them our emperor's might!
皇帝陛下のご威光を
我ら　神聖ブリタニア帝国の力を
The might of our Holy Britannian Empire!
Yイエス　マイ　ロード
Yes, My Lord!
上からも来た　これじゃあ…
They're coming from above, too! This is!
そうだな　カラレス総督が出てきたのだろう
That's right.
Viceroy Calares must have arrived.
脱出は難しい
Escape will be difficult. Which is why...
だから　私の勝ちだ
I'm going to win.
第2次突入部隊は　Jフロアまで　制圧完了
Assault team 2 now has control up to floor J!
黒の騎士団に残された脱出ルートは　一つのみです
That leaves only one escape
route left for the Black Knights.
しかし　そこには　我々本隊が陣取っている
However, that's where our main force is camped.
はい
Right. All we need to do is drive them to us.
あとは　追い立てるだけです
報道の手配をしておけ
Set up a broadcast with the media.
テロリストには　公開処刑がふさわしい
A public execution of terrorists
is most appropriate.
敵は勝利を確信しているはずだ
The enemy must be certain of their victory.
条件はクリアされつつある
That clears all the conditions.
あとは　そちらのフロアだが
All that's left is your floor, correct?
10分以内かな
We should be finished in 10 minutes.
分かった
Understood. Then we'll stand by here and defend it.
ならば　今の配置で守りきれる
ディートハルトの仕込みは
What about Diethard's preparations?
システムは生きていた
The system's still running.
すべては　作戦に基づいて…
Everything's going according to plan.
こちらB2　敵のナイトメアが1機で
This is B2!
A single enemy Knightmare is... Agh!
どうした
What's wrong?
そんな　さっきまで…
But, that's... It was just there!
B2　なんだ？
B2? What's going on?
敵はIFFを外しているのか
Has an enemy deactivated his I.F.F.?
And he's operating on his own?
しかも　単独行動
ゼロ　こちらP6　敵が
Zero, this is P6!
The enemy is! It's... AGH!!!
敵が…
P6
P6!
こちらR5　R1がやられて
This is R5! They got R1!
まずい　このままでは　こちらに
Not good. At this rate,
he's headed right for me!
ゼロ　ひとまず　あんただけでも逃げてくれ
Zero! At the very least,
you have to get out of here!
もともと我らが陽動　捨て石の作戦だ
We're basically decoys, sacrificial
pawns for the plan. So, please...
ならば…
違うな
You're wrong.
間違っているぞ　卜部
You're mistaken, Urabe.
切り捨てるという発想だけでは　ブリタニアには勝てない
If you consider yourselves expendable,
you'll never beat the Britannians.
卜部隊長
Capt. Urabe!
行けそうか
Can you get there?
はい　物質搬入口ですね
Yeah. The cargo loading dock, right?
ああ
Right. That's a shortcut to get to this floor.
このフロアに来るためには　そこが近道だ
確認しました
It's confirmed.
ランスロットを基にした量産試作機かと
It looks like a mass-production
unit based on the Lancelot.
そうか　しかし　今は　捕縛のときではない
I see. Still, this is no time
to try capturing it. Destroy it.
破壊しろ
分かりました
Understood.
えっ　消えた？
It vanished?!
うわっ…なんで　こっちに
How'd it get over here?!
待て　消えたとは　どういうことだ
Wait! What do you mean it disappeared?!
C.C.　そちらのフロアはまだ終わらないのか
C.C.! Isn't your floor finished yet?
何を慌てている　そっちにはカレンと卜部がいるだろう
Why are you panicking?
You have Kallen and Urabe with you, don't you?
こいつか　イレギュラーは
That's it? The aberration?!
ふざけるな
Don't make me laugh!
スザクじゃあるまいし　戦略が戦術につぶされてたまるものか
You aren't Suzaku,
and tactics cannot defeat strategy!
近接戦闘なら　こっちが上だ
We've got the advantage in close-range combat!
遅い
Too slow!
消えた…本当に
It vanished! It really vanished!
神速
Fast as a god!
ありえない
Impossible... It's not physically possible!
物理的なものではない　何か別の…
It must be something else!
や…やられる
It... It's going to get me!
卜部
Urabe!
卜部さん
ゼロ　お前の正体が学生であろうとかまわない
Zero, I don't care if you're really a student!
「切り捨てるだけでは」と言ったその言葉
You weren't lying when you
said we weren't expendable!
紅月
Kouzuki!
はい
Yes?
ゼロを頼む
Protect Zero.
He's the last hope we have left.
彼だけが残された希望だ
すまんな　ラクシャータ
Forgive me, Rakshata...
ゼロよ
Zero! Save Japan!
日本を　民を拾ってやって　ほし～い
Rally our people once more!
四聖剣とは　虚名にあらず
We don't call ourselves the Four Holy Swords...
just because the name is cool!
卜部
Urabe...
Damn. He used that
instantaneous movement again?
また　瞬間移動か
ま　待て
No, wait!
私も決めなきゃ
I have to do something impressive, too.
This is for Zero.
ゼロのためにね
残念なお知らせだ
Unfortunately, I can now
report that we're all finished.
準備が整った
そうか
I see. Urabe, your sacrifice
for this moment wasn't in vain.
卜部　お前がつくったこの刹那
ムダではなかった
テロリストめ　まさか自決を
Damned terrorists!
I didn't think they'd opt for suicide!
文化なき猿が
Uncivilized monkeys!
全機　ロスト　全機　通信途絶しました
All units, lost!
- Contact lost with all units!
- Wh-What the?!
うわっ　なんだ
認識非常レベルCに変更
Confirm voice communication,
then go to emergency level C!
インターセプトから1500まで上昇後　旋回に入ります
Ascending from intercept
to 1500 and circling!
そうか　これで　上にいる敵は地面にたたきつけられて
I see! This will smash the enemies
above us to the ground!
それだけではない
Not just that.
バ　バカな
Im... Impossible!
脱出ルートを絞ったのが過ちだったな
Your mistake was to
block our escape route.
君の居場所を教えているようなものじゃないか
Which practically advertised
your position to me!
さよなら　カラレス総督
Goodbye, Viceroy Calares.
総督がやられた？
The viceroy's been killed?!
コーンウェル卿は　どこに
Where's Lord Cornwell?!
総督ともども…
He was with the viceroy.
じゃあ　指揮系統は
Then who's next in the chain of command?
内務省の　文官に任せよと？
The Minister of Internal Affairs.
You'd hand this over to a civil official?!
うろたえている場合か
This is no time to panic!
私が指揮を執る
I am taking command!
This is not a grab for political power!
これは権力の掌握ではない　あくまで　一時的な措置だ
This is just a temporary measure!
我が姫様の名に懸けて誓おう
I swear it in the
name of my princess!
協力してもらいたい
I ask for your cooperation!
姫様？
Princess?
コーネリア皇女殿下のことか
Does he mean Princess Cornelia?
なら
In that case...
うむ
Right.
イエス　マイ　ロード
Yes, My Lord!
ありがとう　感謝する
Thank you. I'm grateful to you.
では　私は　現場に向かい　救出の指揮を執る
Now then, I'll head to the scene
to direct rescue operations.
アルフレッドは警察を
Alfred, you contact the police.
Bart, you remain here.
バートはここで
あれは…
Th-That's!
どうした
What's wrong?
私は　ゼロ
I am Zero!
えぇ…おいおい　これ　何
Huh?
Whoa, whoa! What the?! No way!
うそ
ゼロでしょう
Isn't that Zero?
死んだはずじゃ
No way!
I thought he was dead!
でも　どうしていきなり…
But, what's brought this on?
まさか本物？
It can't be the real one, can it?
日本人よ　私は帰って来た
People of Japan, I have returned!
映像を止めろ
Kill the video!
ダメです　信号を受け付けません
I can't! It won't take my access code!
私が仕掛けた　ラインオメガ
The Line Omega I set up!
これを知っているのは…
And the only one who knows about it is...
ゼロ！
ZERO!
やはり　あなたは生きていた
I knew you were still alive!
聞け　ブリタニアよ
Hear me, Britannia! Pay close attention,
all of you who have power!
かつ目せよ
力を持つ　すべての者たちよ
私は悲しい
I am sad.
戦争と差別
War and discrimination.
Evil intentions brandished by the strong.
振りかざされる強者の悪意
間違ったまま　たれ流される　悲劇と喜劇
The same mistaken discharge
of tragedy and comedy.
世界は何一つ変わっていない
The world has not changed one bit!
だから　私は復活せねばならなかった
And that is why I had to reawaken!
強き者が弱き者を虐げ続けるかぎり
So long as the strong oppress the
weak, my rebellion will continue!
私は抗い続ける
まずは愚かなるカラレス総督に
Beginning with the divine punishment I brought
down just now upon the foolish Viceroy Calares!
たった今　天誅を下した
おやおや　いきなりやってくれるねぇ
Man, oh man. The Elevens' king sure popped
back up with a vengeance. Huh, Suzaku?
イレヴンの王様は
なぁ　スザク
出ました　発信元は　中華連邦総領事館です
Got it! The signal is originating from
the Chinese Federation consulate!
中華連邦の？
The Chinese Federation's?
まさか　亡命？
Has he defected?
どうやって包囲網を
How did they break through our encirclement?
そうか
Of course! They went inside the fallen building!
ヤツら　倒れたビルの中を
バベルタワーを道に見立てて
They chose to make Babel Tower itself their path!
では　中華連邦は
But then, what about the Chinese Federation?
事前に話がついていた？　バカな
Did they both set this up beforehand...
Impossible!
なぁ　死んだんだろ　ゼロは
C'mon, Zero's dead, isn't he?
ああ
Yeah.
じゃあ　偽者か？
Then this is a fake?
どちらにしても　総領事館に突入すれば
Either way, if we break into the consulate...
重大なルール違反だ
We'd be breaking a vital rule.
It'd cause an international incident.
国際問題になるぞ
ゼロを名乗っている以上　皇族殺しだ
As long as he's calling himself Zero,
he's guilty of killing royalty.
EUとの戦いも大事だけどさ
That makes it as important
as our war with the E.U.
どっちでも　アリ地獄
It's a slippery slope, either way.
総督殺害と逃走ルートの確保
Killing the viceroy and
securing our escape route...
同時に実現するなんて
He was able to do
both at the same time!
この知力　大胆さ
His intellect... It's astounding.
ゼロだ　本物の
It's Zero! The real one!
私は戦う
I shall fight! Fight all those
who use power mistakenly!
間違った力を行使するすべての者たちと
故に私はここに　合衆国日本の建設を再び宣言する
Therefore...
I once again...
here and now declare the founding
of the United States of Japan!
よろしいのですか
Are you sure about this?
This is not the empress's direct order.
天子様の勅旨でもないというのに
私が決めたことに　不満でも
You are dissatisfied with my decision?
いえ　別に
No. Never mind.
ゼロよ　あなたのためなら
Oh, Zero... Because of you,
the United States of...
「合衆国…
…日本」
Japan...
テロリストが国を？
The terrorists will form a nation?
この瞬間より
From this moment, this room shall
be the first dominion of the U.S.J.!
この部屋が　合衆国日本の最初の領土となる
たったひと部屋の国とはね
A nation consisting of just one room!
相変わらず　面白い男
That man's as amusing as ever!
人種も主義も宗教も問わない
Race, ideology, and religion will not matter!
国民たる資格はただ一つ
Being a citizen will have but one requirement!
正義を行うことだ
To do that which is just!
これより先は　我が中華連邦の領土となるが
You realize what happens if you move past here...
onto Chinese Federation
consular grounds, don't you?
分かった
All right. We'll meet in a diplomatic conference later.
後日　外交の場で　お会いしよう
ゼロ
Zero... How useful will he prove to us in the end?
果たして彼の利用価値は
ブリタニア軍なら　すでに　お帰りいただいた
If you're a Britannian soldier,
you've already been asked to leave.
それとも　ゼロの身内の者かな？
Or are you one of Zero's followers?
さぁ　どちらなんでしょう
I'm not sure. Which am I?
謎かけは　好みではない
I'm not terribly fond of riddles.
ええ　僕もそうですよ
Yes, I'm exactly the same way, myself.
知りたいんです　真実を
What I want to know is the truth.
だから　殺しに来ました　ゼロを
That's why I came.
To kill Zero.
胸の中 いつか拾った
Mune no naka itsuka hirotta
Someday let's try to pick up and rebuild
幸せの欠片 集めてみよう
Shiawase no kakera atsumete miyou
The fragments of happiness in our hearts
忘れかけていたメロディー
Wasurekaketeita melody
That nearly forgotten melody
色褪せず僕の真ん中に
Iroasezu boku no man'naka ni
Stay vivid, deep inside of me
ありがとう 心から 僕に今があるのはみんなのおかげさ
Arigatou kokoro kara
I thank you from the bottom of my heart
Boku ni ima ga aru no wa minna no okagesa
Everything I have now, I owe to everyone
ありがとう 心から 次は僕がみんなにハッピー贈るよ
Arigatou kokoro kara
I thank you from the bottom of my heart
Tsugi wa boku ga minna ni happy okuru yo
Next I'll send happiness to everyone
何もかも忘れないよ あの日の僕も僕だから
Nanimokamo wasurenai yo
I won't forget anything
Ano hi no boku mo boku dakara
Because I'm still the same as I was that day
「大好きだよ」って　いつも言ってあげなきゃ駄目だね
Daisuki da yo'tte itsumo
You need me to keep on saying
Itte agenakya dame da ne
How much I love you
涙がこぼれそうな長い夜は ふっと振り返って
Namida ga kobore sou na nagai yoru wa
On those long nights, your tears about to overflow
Futto furikaette
Just turn around
足跡を辿るんだ あの日を忘れないように
Ashiato wo tadorun'da
Follow those footprints
Ano hi wo wasurenai you ni
So that you'll never forget that day
ナナリーを捜し出し　守りきるためには　力が必要だ
If I just wait,
the world will never move.
皇帝やスザクよりも強い力が
To find Nunnally and protect her,
I'll need power.
手に入れてみせる
そのためにも　まずは　あいつを
A power stronger than
the emperor and Suzaku.
偽りの弟　ロロを…
I have to try and gain it.
Manipulate with my Geass
to that end.
Using the United States
of Japan as the core,
I will build a world that will surpass Britannia!
And to get that, I must first take care of him.
Of my phony little brother, Rolo.
IMPRISONED IN CAMPUS